A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1 FA389
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Cross Reference Sheets (Broa-Brou), January 4, 1949-April 1, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 195)
- Broadman, Joseph, May 25, 1956-June 1, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 196)
- Brookdale International Institute, January 27, 1972-May 18, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 197)
- Brookings Institution, December 17, 1970-July 18, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 198)
- Brooklyn Botanic Garden, December 20, 1956-February 20, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 199)
- Brooklyn-Cumberland Medical Center (Stanley Bergen), March 24, 1970-January 19, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 200)
- Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, May 18-24, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 201)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Brow-Broz), April 11, 1950-February 10, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 202)
- Brown, Sibyl Clement, June 24, 1969-September 17, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 203)
- Brown University, June 20, 1968-February 13, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 204)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Bru-Bry), February 20, 1961-February 29, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 205)
- Bryn Mawr College, May 15, 1975-June 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 206)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Bua-Buf), February 2, 1951-July 18, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 207)
- University of Buffalo, December 1, 1952-February 11, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 208)
- University of Buffalo, December 1, 1952-February 11, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 209)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Bug-Bun), January 12, 1951-March 11, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 210)
- Building (Commonwealth Fund), December 15, 1953-December 9, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 211)
- Bunnell, Paul W., January 13, 1970-June 18, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 212)
- Bunting, Mary I. (Polly), July 26, 1973-August 14, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 213)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Bur-By), April 29, 1943-September 15, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 214)
- Bushfield, George I., December 15-29, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 215)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cab-Cal), February 6, 1951-July 31, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 216)
- California College of Podiatry, April 27, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 217)
- California Institute of Technology, August 13, 1951-November 8, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 218)
- California Medical Association, August 16, 1956-January 5, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 219)
- California State Department of Mental Health, May 19-21, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 220)
- California State Department of Mental Hygiene (Community Services Survey), September 2, 1951-August 15, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 221)
- California State Department of Public Health, August 26, 1952-May 17, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 222)
- California State University and Colleges (Fresno), April 10, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 223)
- University of California (Berkeley), November 22, 1950-November 8, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 224)
- University of California (Berkeley) - Institute of Child Welfare (Jean MacFarlane), October 19, 1950-July 3, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 225)
- University of California (Berkeley) - School of Public Health, Maternal and Child Health Program (Helen M. Wallace), December 21, 1973-April 30, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 226)
- University of California (Berkeley) - School of Public Health, Maternal and Child Health Program (Helen M. Wallace), December 21, 1973-April 30, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 227)
- University of California (Berkeley and Los Angeles) - School of Public Health, January 24, 1950-May 7, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 228)
- University of California (Davis), April 1, 1969-August 19, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 229)
- University of California (Davis) - Tahoe Workshop, February 28, 1967-March 12, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 230)
- University of California (Irvine), November 10, 1954-January 16, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 231)
- University of California (Irvine) - Orange County Medical Center/Community Health Planning Institute, March 20, 1970-June 23, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 232)
- University of California (Los Angeles) - Edward H. Forgotson, March 5, 1968-August 7, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 233)
- University of California (Los Angeles) - Edward H. Forgotson, March 5, 1968-August 7, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 234)
- University of California (Los Angeles) - Sherman M. Mellinkoff, February 25, 1977-January 10, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 235)
- University of California (Los Angeles) - Hypothalamic Function Throughout the Lifespan - Mary A.B. Brazier, July 8, 1974-September 9, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 236)
- University of California (Los Angeles) - Institute of Neurology and Psychiatry, October 21, 1955-November 15, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 237)
- University of California (Los Angeles) - Medical School, October 24, 1953-April 28, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 238)
- University of California (San Diego and Santa Cruz), June 2, 1964-May 9, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 239)
- University of California (San Francisco) - School of Medicine, October 22, 1951-September 26, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 240)
- University of California (San Francisco) - Washington Office of the Policy Center, April 30, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 241)
- Callahan, Mary E. (Physical Therapy Education Manuscript), November 17, 1965-December 21, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 242)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cam-Cap), January 16, 1951-April 2, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 243)
- Cambridge University (Wolfson College, England), January 14, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 244)
- Campbell, David, August 20, 1957-September 9, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 245)
- Canadian Mental Health Association, September 24, 1951-January 26, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 246)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cara-Caru), October 13, 1944-December 16, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 247)
- Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, May 4, 1970-November 24, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 248)
- Carnegie Corporation of New York, March 12, 1971-March 6, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 249)
- Carstairs, G. Morris, November 4, 1969-August 1, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 250)
  Former Special Foreign Fellow.
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cas-Caz), April 3, 1936-September 21, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 251)
- Case Western Reserve University (School of Medicine), September 8, 1964-November 21, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 252)
- Case Western Reserve University (School of Medicine), September 8, 1964-November 21, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 253)
- Case Western Reserve University (School of Medicine), September 8, 1964-November 21, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 254)
- Case Western Reserve University (School of Medicine), September 8, 1964-November 21, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 255)
- Cassell, Eric J. (New York Hospital/Cornell Medical Center - Effective Communication in Medical Practice), January 29, 1979-October 4, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 256)
- Casterline, Ray L., March 19, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 257)
- Caudill, William, May 28, 1951-August 3, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 258)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ce), November 1, 1950-September 22, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 259)
- Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Sciences, October 25, 1954-September 10, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 260)
- Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange Between East and West, June 13, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 261)
- Center for Information on America (Vital Issues Profile), March 2, 1972-July 24, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 262)
- Center for Political Research, November 23, 1971-December 6, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 263)
- Center for Psychosocial Studies (Chicago - George H. Pollock), December 12, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 264)
- Center for Voluntary Society (Washington, D.C.), September 24, 1970-December 8, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 265)
- Center of Medical Education and Clinical Investigation (Buenos Aires), May 14, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 266)
- Central Intelligence Agency, August 29, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 267)
- Centre D'Exchanges Technologiques Internationaux, October 21, 1965-December 15, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 268)
- Centre for Advanced Study in the Developmental Sciences (England), April 2-9, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 269)
- Centre for the Study of Adolescence (London, England), January 26, 1972-November 15, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 270)
- Centre Royaumont Pour Une Science de L'Homme (Paris, France), January 29, 1974-August 2, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 271)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cha), May 1, 1947-December 18, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 272)
- Chapman, Carleton B., May 14, 1966-November 17, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 273)
- Charlotte Foundation for Research in Patient Care (University of North Carolina), May 1, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 274)
- Charlotte Medical Clinic, December 8, 1970-August 12, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 275)
- Chase, Grace D., November 24, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 276)
- Chase, Grace D., November 24, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 277)
- Chase, Richard Allen, January 18, 1974-April 1, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 278)
- Chase, Robert A., September 9, 1966-November 4, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 279)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Che), June 4, 1952-July 15, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 280)
- Cheng, Tsung O. (George Washington University), February 26, 1973-August 21, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 281)
- Chertok, L., February 1, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 282)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Chi), June 19, 1944-March 11, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 283)
- Chiappo, Leopoldo, June 15, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 284)
- Chicago Medical School/University of Health Science, September 21, 1967-February 26, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 285)
- University of Chicago (Hospital-Hotel Plan), April 7, 1950-December 18, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 286)
- University of Chicago (Institute of Behavioral Sciences - Use of the Base Hospital Study), October 30, 1950-June 29, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 287)
- University of Chicago (Medical School), May 2, 1950-February 25, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 288)
- Children's Hearing and Speech Center (Washington, D.C.), January 28, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 289)
- Children's Hospital Medical Center (Boston), June 17, 1969-November 25, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 290)
- Children's Hospital National Medical Center (Washington, D.C.), July 24, 1970-July 12, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 291)
- Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, February 21, 1949-January 13, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 292)
- Children's Hospital Research Foundation, December 22, 1952-January 23, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 293)
- Children's Memorial Hospital, October 11-13, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 294)
- University of Chile (Francisco Rojas Villegas and Juan Zanartic), October 27, 1967-May 12, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 295)
- Chilgren, Richard A., February 5, 1971-September 29, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 296)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, University of Minnesota, Boxes 207-208, Folders 1937-1952.
- China (People's Republica of China), April 4, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 297)
- China Medical Board, November 10, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 298)
- Chinese University at Hong Kong, December 21, 1966-March 13, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 299)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cho-Chw), May 22, 1950-March 25, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 300)
- Christian Medical Commission (World Council of Churches), April 4-17, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 301)
- Church Health Clinics (Granger Westberg, Wittenberg University), July 29, 1971-May 25, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 302)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ci), January 14, 1950-October 20, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 303)
- University of Cincinnati, September 21, 1951-November 23, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 304)
- Citizens' Commission on Science, Law and the Food Supply (Rockefeller University), February 14, 1974-March 6, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 305)
- City University of New York, December 6, 1968-January 17, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 306)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cla), October 9, 1950-December 9, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 307)
- Claman, Henry, July 26, 1956-September 11, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 308)
- Clare College (Cambridge, England - Sir Eric Ashby), April 20, 1968-December 30, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 309)
- Clark, Katherine, August 26, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 310)
- Clark University, January 21, 1958-February 19, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 311)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cle-Cly), June 15, 1951-March 27, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 312)
- Cleveland Health Museum and Education Center, September 23, 1970-October 22, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 313)
- Cleveland Metropolitan Service Commission, October 29, 1956-November 15, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 314)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Coa-Coh), July 1, 1947-March 9, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 315)
- Coggeshall, Lowell T., March 9-24, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 316)
- Cohen, Ethel, April 11, 1949-April 18, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 317)
- Cohen, Seymour S. (State University of New York, Stony Brook), February 2, 1979-October 7, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 318)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Advanced Medical Fellowships Series, Box 9, Folder 100.
- Cohen, Sol, June 19, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 319)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cola-Colm), January 11, 1949-November 7, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 320)
- Cole, Ralph E. (Medical Associates Research Foundation, Chelmsford, Massachusetts), March 20, 1973-March 11, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 321)
- Coleman, Jules, December 1, 1949-July 25, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 322)
- Colgate University, April 29, 1952-October 16, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 323)
- College Mental Health Center, April 12, 1971-October 6, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 324)
- College of Osteopathic Physicians and Surgeons (Los Angeles), 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 325)
  California College of Medicine as of 1959.
- Collier, Bert David, Jr., December 28, 1973-January 16, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 326)
- Collings, Joseph S., July 23, 1948-April 23, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 327)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Colo-Coly), December 18, 1948-February 18, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 328)
- Colombian Association of the Schools of Medicine, September 29, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 329)
- Colorado Institute on Population Problems (John R. Berningham), June 23-25, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 330)
- University of Colorado, May 11, 1956-March 24, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 331)
- University of Colorado (Home Care Program), December 30, 1948-June 14, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 332)
- University of Colorado (Medical Center - Program in Health Administration, February 16-25, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 333)
- Columbia Presbyterian-Harlem Hospital, February 12, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 334)
- Columbia School of Clinical Medicine (Yakima, Washington), June 4, 1969-June 10, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 335)
- University of Columbia (College of Physicians and Surgeons - Center for Population and Family Health), September 26, 1977-October 7, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 336)
- University of Columbia (College of Physicians and Surgeons - Curriculum Committee Report), June 19-24, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 337)
- University of Columbia (College of Physicians and Surgeons - Health Care Delivery System), January 17, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 338)
- University of Columbia (College of Physicians and Surgeons - Presbyterian Medical Center), April 25, 1950-November 8, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 339)
- University of Columbia (College of Physicians and Surgeons - Presbyterian Medical Center), April 25, 1950-November 8, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 340)
- University of Columbia (College of Physicians and Surgeons - Presbyterian Medical Center), April 25, 1950-November 8, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 341)
- University of Columbia (Cooperative Program - College of Physicians and Surgeons and Athens, Greece), October 14-22, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 342)
- University of Columbia (Department of Biological Sciences - Cyrus Levinthal), May 22, 1968-August 10, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 343)
- University of Columbia (School of Public Health and Administrative Medicine), July 5, 1973-November 5, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 344)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Coma-Communication), 1947-September 18, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 345)
- Commission for the United World Colleges, April 8, 1974-September 12, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 346)
- Commission on Chronic Illness, April 25, 1949-October 14, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 347)
- Commission on Financing Higher Education, April 20, 1951-November 23, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 348)
- Commission on Financing of Hospital Care, December 28, 1951-January 17, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 349)
- Commission on Foreign Medical Graduates, May 8, 1973-June 17, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 350)
- Commission on Non-Traditional Study (New York), March 31, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 351)
- Commission on Physicians for the Future (National), May 29, 1975-December 6, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 352)
- Committee for National Health Insurance (Washington, D.C.), January 8, 1973-February 1, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 353)
- Committee on Atlantic Studies, October 23, 1967-December 15, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 354)
- Committee on Banking and Currency (U.S. House of Representatives), February 7, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 355)
- Committee on Foreign Affairs, September 8, 1964-March 12, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 356)
- Committee on Institutional Cooperation of the Big-Ten Universities, March 13, 1961-October 9, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 357)
- The Common Fund, April 4, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 358)
- "The Common Wealth" Community Funds, Inc., April 5-6, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 359)
- Commonwealth Foundation (London), August 12, 1964-April 18, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 360)
- Commonwealth Fund (50th Anniversary Celebration), January 15, 1968-October 4, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 361)
- Commonwealth Fund (50th Anniversary Celebration), January 15, 1968-October 4, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 362)
- Commonwealth Fund - Carnegie Corporation, February 8, 1966-June 17, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 363)
- Commonwealth Fund - Carnegie Corporation (Study Group Meetings), March 5, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 364)
- Commonwealth Fund of Boston, April 28, 1949-May 20, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 365)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Community-Cond), April 4, 1952-August 18, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 366)
- Community Health Association (United Auto Workers), 1970 (Box 21, Folder 367)
  Transferred to Medical Education, Community Health, Community Health Association United Auto Workers-Detroit.
- Community Health Institute (New York), January 4-10, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 368)
- Community Obstetrical Study, November 21, 1958-May 4, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 369)
- Community Research Associates, December 22, 1953-November 13, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 370)
- Comprehensive Group Health Service (Philadelphia), May 15, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 371)
- Comprehensive Medical Plan, Inc., September 26, 1966-October 28, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 372)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Conf-Cong), December 18, 1948-February 20, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 373)
- Conference - Ethical Aspects of Experimentation on Human Subjects, March 15, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 374)
- Conference - United States Voluntary-Private Sector Strategy, October 10-14, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 375)
- Conference on a National Policy for Urban America, May 3, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 376)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Conl-Conw), January 4, 1950-March 25, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 377)
- Connecticut College, November 9, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 378)
- University of Connecticut (School of Medicine), April 21, 1965-November 4, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 379)
- University of Connecticut (School of Medicine - Charles D. Cook), May 6, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 380)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Coo), May 3, 1950-December 11, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 381)
- Cooper, John A. D., November 10, 1958-January 5, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 382)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cop-Cor), December 14, 1950-September 11, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 383)
- University of Copenhagen, November 1-21, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 384)
- Cornell University, April 4, 1951 to December 28, 1951; July 22, 1960 to July 17, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 385)
- Cornell University, April 4, 1951 to December 28, 1951; July 22, 1960 to July 17, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 386)
- Cornell University (Leo W. Simmons), July 19, 1950-February 9, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 387)
- Cornell University (Medical College - Community Medicine, George Reader), December 16, 1969-July 31, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 388)
- Cornell University (Medical College - Computer Project), January 10-24, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 389)
- Cornell University (New York City Medical Center), November 29, 1944-July 12, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 390)
- Cornell University (Social Analyses of Science Systems - Science, Technology and Society; Frank Rhodes), June 10, 1975-February 18, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 391)
- Corson, John J., September 23, 1966-June 26, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 392)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cos-Coz), February 16, 1951-June 12, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 393)
- Council for Clinical Training, April 17, 1951-April 9, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 394)
- Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., April 29, 1969-October 15, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 395)
- Council for the Advancement of Science Writing, Inc., January 11-26, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 396)
- Council for Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds, July 28, 1954-December 28, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 397)
- Council of Teaching Hospitals - A.A. M.C., May 27, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 398)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cra-Cri), August 21, 1951-October 28, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 399)
- Crane Duplicating Service, January 23, 1963-February 28, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 400)
- Crane, Roger A., September 18, 1964-May 5, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 401)
- Crawley, Paul, October 6-19, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 402)
- Creighton University, May 22, 1963-November 14, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 403)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cro-Cry), April 2, 1949-November 4, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 404)
- Crock, Henry V., May 1, 1968-June 7, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 405)
- Crosby, Emilio (Peruvian University, Cayetano Heredia), May 26, 1969-October 9, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 406)
- Cruickshank, Robert, August 2, 1951-July 31, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 407)
- Crutcher, Roberta, September 9, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 408)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cua-Cur), August 16, 1951-November 7, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 409)
- Cultural Funding in the U.S. (Lee Kinche), August 19, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 410)
- Cummings, Elaine and John, May 7, 1951-January 11, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 411)
- Curran, William J., July 30, 1968-October 29, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 412)
- Current Grants and Approved Renewals to Institutions and Organizations, April 15, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 413)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Cus-Cz), April 21, 1953-July 11, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 414)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Daa-Dam), February 6, 1951-December 30, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 415)
- Daddario, Emilio, April 19, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 416)
- Dalhousie University, January 24, 1957-May 20, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 417)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dan-Dau), October 19, 1945-December 18, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 418)
- Dar es Salaam, Medical School (Tanzania), May 14, 1967-January 4, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 419)
- Dartmouth Medical School, January 15, 1951-November 7, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 420)
- Dartmouth Medical School (Interface), November 10, 1975-February 15, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 421)
- Darvall, Frank Ongley, March 28, 1969-April 3, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 422)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dav), February 27, 1951-September 21, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 423)
- Davenport, Horace W., December 24, 1968-January 3, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 424)
- Davidson College (North Carolina), April 24, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 425)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Daw-Daz), June 18, 1951-January 30, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 426)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dea-Dei), December 14, 1950-February 6, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 427)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dej-Dem), November 26, 1946-December 1, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 428)
- University of Delaware, October 23, 1961-January 5, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 429)
- Universidad Del Valle (Cali - Gerald B. Spurr), April 23-29, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 430)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Den-Des), June 7, 1945-February 19, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 431)
- University of Denver, November 20, 1968-December 27, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 432)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare, August 30, 1971-March 18, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 433)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare, August 30, 1971-March 18, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 434)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Det-Dey), June 22, 1951-February 10, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 435)
- Deuschile, Kurt W., December 11, 1959-December 9, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 436)
- De Vries, Anrie, November 25, 1952-January 5, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 437)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dh-Dif), December 13, 1944-October 7, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 438)
- Diaz, Jose F., April 14, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 439)
- Dickinson College, September 9, 1976-October 11, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 440)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dig-Dj), April 18, 1949-November 8, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 441)
- Distinguished New York "Award Dinner" (Mrs. Albert D. Lasker), October 1-9, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 442)